Dude, today I am going to try VS Money's filter coffee.
These people have come on Shark Tank
season 2 and they also serve
South Indian snacks along with coffee, but I am going to try their copy
because they don't like
filter coffee and this is the same filter coffee
decoration, that is, if you put it in gram milk
and then add sugar, then a good
coffee is made, let's try this too,
this is a 220 ml bottle of coffee
and in it you have to put only 20
or 25 ml of coffee at a time, sugar as per taste,
shares gas
note bad, dude, that means this one bottle costs Rs 145
and you can make coffee worth Rs 8 or 10 from this one bottle.
Now look, I do
n't know about the investment, but the coffee is okay.